Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1948-1983, undated (bulk 1959-1979) MS 3009-RG 6.I MS 3009-RG 6TEST
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Editor-in-Chief: Subseries I.C. Jason McManus Files
  - Subsubseries I.C.3. Departmental Files
    The Departmental Files are McManus's office files on various projects and subjects. Records include invitations to serve on boards (Boy Scouts); articles on the Time Warner merger; protest letters on advertisements published in Time Inc.'s magazines (Condom Ads and Feminist Complaints); memoranda about the information reference services provided by Edit Services; memoranda and reports reviewing problems or required retooling of the magazines ( Fortune: Bias and Time: Task Force); the complaint letter from the staff organization Lesbians and Gay Men at Time Warner with annotations by McManus (Gay Complaints); proposals for collaboration with television networks regarding News on Demand; correspondence about possible book publication (Schwarzkopf); registration materials for the staff softball team; and memoranda discussing the first issue of Martha Stewart Living. The term "memorabilia" in titles refers to papers, not objects. Two archives transfer forms found stapled to the front of files are at the end.
    - Archives/Elaine Felsher, 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Journalists Association, 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 5)
    - Asiaweek: General, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 6-8)
    - Asiaweek: Michael O'Neill, 1989-1994 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 9-11)
    - Asiaweek: Yazhou Zhoukan, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 12)
    - Boston/Mystery Guest Lunch, 1989 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 13)
    - Boy Scouts, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 14)
    - CNN (Turner), 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 15)
    - Connie Bruck: New Yorker Piece, 1992 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 16)
    - Bryson, John, 1988 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 17)
    - Cave, Ray: Memoranda, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 18-19)
    - Clurman, Richard: Time Book, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 20)
    - Compensation, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 21)
    - Condom Ads, 1989 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 22)
    - Corporate Policy Committee Meetings, 1993 (Offsite-box 1204-1205)
    - Custom Publishing, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 2)
    - Donovan, Hedley: General, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 3)
    - Donovan, Hedley: Memoranda, 1970-1976 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 4)
    - Donovan, Hedley: Staff Memoranda, 1967-1978 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 5)
    - Donovan, Hedley: Speeches, 1970-1976 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 6)
    - Edit Management Meeting, 1993 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 7)
    - Edit Services, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 8)
    - Entertainment Weekly, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 9-10)
    - Family Wealth, 1988 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 11-12)
    - Feminist Complaints, 1989 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 13)
    - First Amendment, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 14)
    - Fortune: General, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 15-16)
    - Fortune: Bias, 1990 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 17)
    - Fortune: International, 1989 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 18)
    - Fortune Espana, 1989 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 19)
    - Fortune France: General, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 20)
    - Fortune France: Board Meetings, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 21-22)
    - Fortune Italia, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 1)
    - Gay Complaints, 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 2)
    - Globe Review, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 3)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Memoranda, 1951-1978 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 4-8)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Retirement, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 9)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Speeches, 1968-1987 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 10-11)
    - Guild, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 12)
    - Gulf War Coverage, 1991 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 13)
    - Halasz, Piri, 1987 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 14)
    - HBO, 1989 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 15)
    - In Style, 1994 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 16)
    - Interns, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 17)
    - International Press Institute, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 18)
    - Kamsky, Ginny: China Project, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 19)
    - Library, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 20)
    - Life, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 21-22)
    - Life Weekly, 1991 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 23-24)
    - Little, Brown, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 1)
    - Luce, Henry, III, 1994 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 2)
    - Luce, Henry: Biographer, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 3)
    - March of Time: Musical Adaptation Outline, 1978 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 4)
    - Magazine Group Strategy, 1987 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 5)
    - Maidstone Management Meeting, 1989 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 6-7)
    - Man of the Year Booklet by National Portrait Gallery, 1987 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 8)
    - McManus in Paris for Time Europe Launch, 1973 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 9)
    - McManus/Norman Pearlstine Dinner, 1994 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 10)
    - Memorabilia, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 11-12)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 13)
    - Mentoring, 1993 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 14)
    - Miller, Bob, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 15)
    - Money, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 16-17)
    - Morrison Special Projects, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 18)
    - Muller, Henry, 1992 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 19)
    - New Magazines/Joint Ventures, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 20-21)
    - News on Demand, 1993 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 22-23)
    - 1968 Project, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 24)
    - 1980 Committee, 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 25)
      Includes Edit Task Force material.
    - Pan Am 103 Story in Time, 1992 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 1)
    - Patricia Ryan Salute from Ann Fadiman, 1987 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 2)
    - Papandreou, Andreas, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 3)
    - People, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 4-5)
    - President's Advisory Panel on International Edicational Exchange, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 6)
    - Roger Rosenblatt/Steve Ross Letters, 1992 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 7)
    - Ross, Steve, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 8)
    - Russian Meeting (Publishing Committee USSR), 1988 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 9)
    - Salzburg Seminar, 1992 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 10)
    - Schiavone Construction Company, 1990 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 11)
    - Schwarzkopf, H. Norman, 1991 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 12)
    - Softball, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 13)
    - South Africa, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 14)
    - Sports Illustrated: General, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 15-16)
    - Sports Illustrated: Swim Suit Issue, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 17)
    - Sports Illustrated for Kids, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 18)
    - Stewart, Martha, 1990 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 19)
    - Takeover Suggestions from Staff, 1989 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 20)
    - Thank You Notes and Complaints, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 21)
    - Time: General, 1986-1994 (Offsite-box 1208-1209)
    - Time: Articles On, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 2)
    - Time: Lloyd Cutler on Kramer Piece, 1994 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 3)
    - Time: Polish in SS, 1994 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 4)
    - Time: Task Force, 1991 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 5-7)
    - Time Australia, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 8-9)
    - Time Canada, 1993 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 10)
    - Time Nihonban, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 11)
    - Time Inc.: Articles on Time Inc. Strike, 1976 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 12)
    - Time Inc.: Speeches, 1970-1988 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 13)
    - Time Warner: Board Meeting: Lyford Cay, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 14-15)
    - Time Warner: Books About, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 16)
    - Time Warner: Merger: In-House Stories, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 17)
    - Time Warner: Merger: Outside Stories, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 18)
    - Time Warner: Merger: Bernstein New York Times Article, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 19)
    - Time Warner: Merger: Brucker New Yorker Article, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 20)
    - Together Dummy, 1983 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 1)
    - TV Cable Week: Postmortem, 1983 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 2)
    - TV Cable Week: Task Force, 1983 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 3)
    - United Way, 1993 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 4)
    - Video Weekly, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 5-6)
    - Wall Street Journal Article on CEO Pay Survey/Graf Crystal, 1991 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 7)
    - Wall Street Journal on Time, 1993 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 8)
    - Watergate Memorabilia, 1974 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 9)
    - Who ( People Australia), 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 10)
    - Woman Dummy, 1977 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 11)
    - Archives Transfer Forms, 1994 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 23)
  - Subsubseries I.C.4. Trips, 1986-1992
    Trips contains business travel files and include correspondence, itineraries, background information on people and places, travel notes from McManus and others, and copies of travel documents.
    - 1986 May: France, Germany, Moscow (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 12)
    - 1986 November: Far East (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 13)
    - 1987-1988: China, Hong Kong, Japan (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 14)
    - 1988 February: London and Milan with Reginald Brack (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 15)
    - 1988 November: Paris and Milan (Fortune France and Fortune Italia) (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 16)
    - 1990 April: Eastern European Countries and Soviet Union with Henry Muller, ____Stacks, and Reginald Brack (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 17)
    - 1990 May: New York, Moscow, Paris, Cannes (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 18)
    - 1990 September: Los Angeles and San Francisco with Richard Stolley and Gil Rogin (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 19)
    - 1990 November-December: Moscow (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 20)
    - 1991 February: Lyford Cay Corporate Policy Committee Meeting (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 21)
    - 1992 Fall: Hong Kong (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 22)
- Series II. Editorial Director: Subseries II.A. _____
  - Subsubseries II.A.1 _____
  - Subsubseries II.A.2 _____
- Series III. Corporate Editor: Subseries III.A. _____
- Series III. Corporate Editor: Subseries III.B. _____